cir.ca 2013-06-19

# Circa News App | Privacy Policy

_Last Updated: September 28, 2012_

Here is Circa's policy regarding the information that we collect and use in connection with delivering our App, your registration with us, and your use of the App and our service. Our policy may change from time to time, and you should check our website periodically for any updates.

Our policy applies only to the App and the service we provide. It doesn't apply to services you use to obtain our App, to services of others that you might find by using our App, or to other services that may coexist with our App or interact with it either on a mobile device or on the Internet (such as Facebook or Twitter). To learn more about other companies' policies, please consult them.

Our policy also does not apply to other companies that might acquire our assets (including our user information), absorb us, or control us. We can't control what others do in those situations.

**What information do we collect and use?**

_Account Information_. When you sign up with us we'll collect certain limited information to identify and reach you, such as your name and email address, as well as your chosen username and password to authenticate your access to our service. We may also collect information about your other accounts, such as your login credentials and other information regarding your accounts on Facebook and Twitter, that may interact with our service. We may in the future also collect information about your relationships with other users on social media services that interact with our service.

_Information About Your Use of Our Service_. We may have access to, and collect, information that your computer or mobile device transmits to us in the course of our interactions, such as the IP address from which you access our service and information about the configuration or identity of any device or computer that you use to interact with us. We collect certain information through the use of tokens such as "cookies," which are small text files that your browser or device saves when you access our service. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to identify that you've logged in to the service and to tell us how and when you interact with our services. We may collect information about what content or information you have accessed, viewed, followed, marked, annotated, commented on, or shared, and how you have done it. That includes both content or information on our service and content or information to which our service links or leads you. We may also use cookies for other purposes, such as to monitor usage and traffic routing on our Services, to customize and improve our services, and to provide information to allow us to analyze and explain our business. We may also use your information for purposes, not discussed here, that we may explain during your use of our services.

**How do we use your information?** We will use your information in a variety of ways in order to provide and improve the service, to personalize the service to you, to deliver content, to connect you with other services you use, and to share certain information externally as we discuss below. In addition, we may use information about groups of users, without focusing on any particular user's information, for a wide variety of business reasons, such as to study usage and traffic patterns, to test different aspects of our technology and service, to analyze and describe our business, and to change our App and our service.

**What Information May We Reveal?** We may publicly reveal personal information that you have publicly revealed on our service, such as comments, annotations, and other information that you explicitly ask us to share or publicize.

We may share any information with other services that you have relationships with, based on information you have given us about those service relationships.

We may engage others to work with us to administer and provide our technology and service. These third-parties may have access to your information only for the purpose of assisting us, and we would furnish them your information only with an obligation of confidentiality commensurate with our own policies.

We may reveal aggregated information of our users and non-identifying information about any user with others for any purpose.

Information that we collect from our users, including personal information, is a business asset. This means that if we go out of business or seek bankruptcy protection, or if another company acquires us, someone else may take possession of the information.

We may reveal information to satisfy or comply with any law, regulation or legal process or to respond to lawful requests, including subpoenas, litigation discovery requests, warrants or court orders; to protect our property, rights and safety and the rights, property and safety of third parties or the public in general; and to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical.

**The Security of Your Information** We take reasonable measures to protect the information that we collect from or about you from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Please be aware, however, that no method of transmitting information over the Internet or storing information is completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of any information.

**Links to Other Sites** Our service may contain links to other websites and services. Any information that you provide on or to a third-party website or service is provided directly to the owner of the website or service and is subject to that party's privacy policy. Our privacy policy does not apply to such websites or services and we're not responsible for the content, privacy or security practices and policies of those websites or services. To protect your information we recommend that you carefully review the privacy policies of other websites and services that you access.

**Modifying Your Information** If you want us to delete your account, please contact us at <http://circa.desk.com/> with your request. We'll take steps to delete your name and email address records as soon as is practicable, but some information may remain in archived/backup copies for our records or as otherwise required by law.

**Our Policy Toward Children** Our Services are not directed to children under 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected personal information of a child under 13 we will take steps to delete such information from our files as soon as possible, which may require terminating an account.

**Changes to Privacy Policy** We may modify and revise this policy from time to time. If we make any material changes to this policy, we'll notify you of such changes by posting them on our website or by sending you an email or other notification, and we'll indicate when such changes will become effective.

**Questions?** Please contact us at <http://circa.desk.com/> if you have any questions about our privacy policy.
